-我准备好了  -你确定
- I'm ready. - You sure?
我帮你把头盔戴好
Let me just straighten out your helmet there.
-谢谢爸爸  -只有一个爸爸  两个妈妈
- Thanks, Daddy. - No, no. One daddy, two mommies.
-好了  你去吧  -没问题
- All right, it's all yours. - Okay, okay.
好样的  好样的
There you go, there you go.
本的第一辆两轮自行车  太激动人心了
Wow, Ben's first big-kid's bike. This is so exciting!
我还记得我学骑车的时候
Oh, yeah, I remember mine.
我6岁的生日  我爸爸带我去公园
It was my sixth birthday. My dad took me to the park...
-坐上脚踏车  它就垮了  -没错
- ...and I got on it, and it bent. - Yeah.
-我从来没有属于自己的脚踏车  -什么
- I never had a bike of my own. - What?
我们家很穷
We didn't have a lot of money.
但对街的女孩有一辆最酷的脚踏车
But the girl across the street had the best bike.
它是粉红色的
It was pink, and it had
手挂着五颜六色的流苏
rainbow-colored tassels hanging off the handles...
还有铃档  一个白色的车筐
...and a bell and this big, white wicker basket...
上面还有塑料小雏菊
...with those plastic daisies stuck on.
听起来很像是我的第一辆脚踏车
That sounds like my first bike.
我爸把他旧的脚踏车送给我
My dad gave me his old one.
-那姑娘让你骑她的车吗  -不
- Did the girl ever let you ride it? - No.
但她把装脚踏车的纸箱送给我
But she gave me the box that it came in.
纸箱前面印了脚踏车的照片
It had a picture of the bike on the front.
我可以坐在上面
So I would sit on it,
我继父会拖着我在后院跑
and my stepdad would drag me around the backyard.
太不公平了
That is so unfair.
挺公平的  我也会拖着他跑
Not really, I got to drag him around too.
你们在干什么
Hey, what are you guys doing?
给邻居做万圣节的糖果
Making holloween candies for the neighbors.
抱歉  你说谁
I'm sorry, who?
我要在门上挂一个篮子
I'm gonna hang a basket on the door.
邻居经过就可以拿块糖
When the neighbors walk by, they can take a piece.
-我们又不认识他们  -我认识
- But we don't know the neighbors. - I do.
有一个长着小胡子的男人
There's, let's see, the guy with the mustache...
老烟枪女士  还有几个小孩
...smokes-a-lot lady, some kids I've seen...
还有一个不喜欢被叫做"锈哥"的红头发男人
...and a red-haired guy who does not like to be called Rusty.
这就是我要做糖果的原因
See, this is exactly why I'm making this candy.
改善邻里关系  了解邻居背景
We can learn their names and get to know our neighbors.
我们搬家不是更快
Wouldn't it be easier if we just moved?
早啊
Good morning!
-有人心情不错  -我为什么要心情不好
- Somebody's in a good mood. - Well, why shouldn't I be?
我有很棒的朋友  有很棒的工作
I have great friends. I have a wonderful job...
而且可以在办公室跟助理鬼混
Where you can make out with your assistant.
那没有什么大不了的
It's not a big deal.
我们彻夜未眠
We stayed up all night
就为了保证我们的交往无后顾之忧
creating a plan so that us dating won't be a problem.
是吗  你要怎么做
Oh, yeah? What's the plan?
我们  我们不会
We... We are not...
让交往
...going to let it...
成为一个问题
...be a problem.
这就是你们彻夜未眠想出的方法
It took you all night to come up with that plan?
我们还忙了些别的
Well, you know, we did other stuff too.
你们俩
Did you two...?
得了  莫妮卡
Oh, Monica, come on.
我不会在第一次约会时就和男伴上床的
You know I don't sleep with guys on the first date.
马特·怀尔  马克·林  本·怀斯
Matt Wire, Mark Lynn, Ben Wise...
现在不了
Anymore!
泰格  我今天有电话会议对吧
Hi, Tag, I have a conference call today, is that correct?
-没错  四点  -谢谢你  没事了
- Yes, at 4. - Okay, thank you, that'll be all.
等等
Wait, wait.
你看到了吗   邮递员没发现
Did you see that? That mail guy had no idea...
我们在恋爱
...there was something going on between us.
-我得回去工作了  -好吧  工作狂
- I'd better get back to my desk. - Okay, hard worker.
我会在你的评估表里提到的
I'll remember to put that in your evaluation.
-我的什么   -你已经工作两个月了
- My what? - You've been here for two months now.
你的上司必须为你做评估
And your boss is required to hand in a performance evaluation.
还有一件我没有评估的事情
But you know, there is one thing that I have yet to evaluate.
-你认真的吗  -不我一直都想这么做
- Are you serious? - No, I've just always wanted to do that.
能帮我收拾下吗
Can you help me clean this up?
篮子都空了  邻居都吃光了
The basket is totally empty! The neighbors ate it all!
要不然是邻居吃了
Well, either that or...
乔伊
Joey!
怎么了
Yeah?
-给邻居的糖是你吃了吗  -本来是要吃
- Did you eat all the neighbor candy? - That was the plan.
当等我看见  就只剩几块了
When I got to it, there was only a few pieces left.
一整天都有人来  他们都很喜欢
They've come by all day. They love it.
他们喜欢我的糖
They love my candy?
-天啊  我得多做一点  -嘿  莫妮卡
- Oh, man, I gotta go make more. - Hey, Mon.
千层面也多做点
You might want to make some more lasagna too.
也许有人很喜欢吃也不一定
Something might have happened to have a huge chunk of it.
罗斯  我的糖被邻居吃光了
Ross, the neighbors ate all my candy.
我的邻居会偷我的报纸
Mine stole my newspaper.
简直是犯罪风潮
It's like a crime wave.
菲比你有时间吗
Pheebs, you got a second?
有啊
Sure.
自从你告诉我有关你脚踏车的故事
Ever since you told me about that bike...
它就在我脑中挥之不去
...I couldn't stop thinking about it.
大家都该有第一辆脚踏车  所以
I mean, everyone should have a first bike, you know? So...
天啊  罗斯
Oh, my God, Ross!
-你喜欢吗   -我爱死它了
- You like it? - I love it!
-是吗  -天啊
- Yeah? - Oh, oh, God...
我也爱你
And I love you.
不是那种爱
Not that way.
但这辆脚踏车让你跟我更亲近了
But the bike got you a lot closer.
把它弄到楼下去
Well, take it downstairs.
试骑一下
You know, give it a test drive.
好的  我的天啊
Okay. Oh, my God.
我的第一辆脚踏车
My first bike!
谢谢你  这是我收过最棒的礼物
Thank you for the best present I've ever gotten.
不客气
You're welcome.
钱德勒快哭了
Oh, and Chandler's about to cry.
我才没有
Am not.
是谁
Who is that?
别担心  我很勇敢
Don't worry, I'm brave.
我很勇敢
I... I am brave.
不不不
No, no, no, no!
请问你是谁
Can you tell me who is there, please?
我叫盖瑞  我住在楼上
My name's Gary. I live upstairs.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
-你知道现在几点了吗  -糖果时间
- Do you know what time it is? - It's candy time.
我室友说你的糖尝起来像是天上掉下来的礼物
My roommate says they taste like little drops of heaven.
别这么夸我
Oh, please.
你听到了吗  "天上掉下来的礼物"
Did you hear that? "Little drops of heaven."
凌晨4点啊
Four a. m.
你能给我一点糖果吗
So can I get some candy?
对不起  但我们之中有人还得早起去上班
I am sorry, but some of us have to get up early and go to work.
他不知道我不是"那个人"
He does not know that I am not "Some of us."
抱歉  明早我会做的
I'm sorry, but I'll put some out in the morning.
好  那我等会再来
Okay, I'll swing by later.
你在这栋住吗
You live in this building?
我觉得我应该记得你才对
Seems like I'd remember you.
晚安  盖瑞
Night, Gar.
你看了你的评估表吗
So did you read your evaluation yet?
上面标着"机密"
No, it was marked "Confidential."
所以我送去人力资源部了
I just sent it to human resources.
你开玩笑的对吧
Please, you're kidding, right?
那是为了开你玩笑写的
I wrote that one as a joke for you.
人力资源部能看喜欢吗
A joke they would appreciate?
我不这么觉得
I'm thinking, no.
-你说了什么  -我说你吻技高超
- What did you say? - I said you were a good kisser...
还有我喜欢你那小屁屁
...and that I liked your teeny, tiny tushy.
不  别提我的屁股啊
No, not my tushy.
后面更糟
It gets worse.
你的积极性  我写
About your initiative, I wrote:
"无需监督  他就可解开我的内衣搭钩"
"He was able to unook my bra with minimal supervision."
表现不佳的方面  我写"千万不要啊"
Under problems with performance, I wrote, "Dear God, I hope not."
之后我画了一些笑脸
And then... and then I drew a little smiley face.
还画了幅小春宫图
And then a small pornographic sketch.
你送菲比脚踏车真的太贴心了
That is so sweet of you to get Phoebe that bike.
我听到那个故事时  差点就哭了
When I heard the story, I almost cried.
差点哭了
Almost cried, huh?
你听到了吗 钱德勒  "差点"哭了
Hear that, Chandler? "Almost" Cried.
只要有人提到《泰坦尼克》你每次都会哭
Hey, you cry every time somebody talks about Titanic.
他们两个只有彼此
Those two had only each other.
菲比很喜欢那脚踏车对吧
Phobe really likes the bike, huh?
我看到她推着它在街边走
Oh, yeah. I saw her walking it down the street the other day.
她的篮子里面还有花  那真的很美
She had these flowers in the basket. It was so cute.
早上我看见她推着它在公园散步
I saw her this morning, walking it by the park.
慢着  她推着脚踏车走
Wait, she was walking the bike?
两次都是
Both times?
-菲比  -嗨
- Hey, Pheebs. - Oh, hi!
-喜欢那辆脚踏车吗  -太喜欢了
- Hey, so you enjoying the bike? - Oh, so much.
菲比  你会骑脚踏车吧
Pheebs, you do know how to ride a bike, don't you?
当然
Of course.
我们能看你骑脚踏车吗
Can we see you ride it?
好
Okay.
看
See?
我早就跟你说不要跟助理交住
I told you not to get involved with your assistant.
纸包不住火的
There's no such thing as a secret when it comes to affairs.
你听到了吗   钱德勒
Did you hear that, Chandler?
纸包不住火
No such thing.
怎么了  我在吃糖
What happened? I'm just eating candy.
或许没有那么糟糕
Maybe it's not that bad.
他们可能看不懂我的意思
They might not take it the way I meant it.
当然了  因为"小屁屁"有屁股
Absolutely, you know? Because "Tushy" Can mean both ass...
和努力工作的员工的意思
...and good worker.
我得把评估表拿回来
I just gotta get the thing back.
瑞秋  你那副小春宫图
Rach? That sketch you mentioned?
看上去像这幅吗
Might it have looked a little like this?
天啊  乔伊
Oh, my God, Joey!
-你是怎么了  -天啊
- What is the matter with you? - God!
买不起成人光碟前  这点天赋还挺有用的
This little talent came in handy before I could afford porn.
对不起  我知道现在是休息时间
Hi, I'm sorry. I know it's after-hours,
但我真的需要糖果
but I really need candy.
抱歉  无能为力  规矩就是规矩
I'm sorry, I can't help you. See? Rules are rules.
拜托了  我有外地客人
Please, I have people coming from out of town today.
-我跟他们提起你的糖果  -你开玩笑呢吧
- I told them all about your candy. - You're kidding.
外地  你怎么说的
Out-of-towners, huh? What did you tell them?
我说你的糖果简直是无与伦比的美味
I told them your candy was absolutely indescribable.
有人说
Some people have said
那是"天上掉下的礼物"  但无所谓了
it's "Little drops of heaven. " But whatever.
拜托  你不能帮帮我吗
Please, can't you help me out?
钱德勒勒  我们认识那位女士吗
Hey, Chandler, do we know that lady?
她不是住你楼下嘿咻时声音超大的那位吗
Isn't she the woman who lives below you and has sex really loud?
仅此一次
All right, I'll do it just this once.
-别告诉别人  -给我吧
- But you can't tell anyone. - Please, just give it to me.
是她没错
Yeah, that's her.
-谢谢  -难以置信啊
- Thank you. - Unbelievable!
我不敢相信那标识没有用
I can't believe that sign didn't work.
你知道什么才会有用吗  别再做糖果了
You know what would work? Stop making candy.
但是他们喜欢
But they like it.
你是说他们喜欢你
You mean they like you.
也许
Maybe.
所以你才当厨师是吧  好让人们喜欢你
Is that why you became a chef, so people would like you?
你真想讨论
You want to talk about
这个讨喜的问题是吧  幽默男
getting people to like you, huh, funny man?
记住我教你的事  你会没事的
Just remember everything I taught you, and you'll be fine.
好吗   开始吧
Okay? Here we go.
预备  开始
Ready, set...
等一下  这个座包真的很不舒服
Wait, this seat is really uncomfortable.
也许开始练习前  我们可以去换一个
Maybe before we start we should just get another one.
也许飞机座椅和懒人椅都行
Perhaps like an airplane seat, or a beanbag chair!
你逃不掉的  你得学骑车
You can't get out of this. You have to learn how to ride a bike.
为什么  我为什么必须得学
Why? Why do I have to learn?
-以防万一  -防哪种万一
- Well, in case of an emergency. - What kind of emergency?
万一一个人走过来
Well, what if a man comes along
拿枪指着你的头说
and puts a gun to your head and says:
"快骑车否则"
"You ride this bike or I'll...
"否则我就开枪"呢
I'll shoot you."
我会按铃分散他的注意力
I would ring the bell to distract him.
然后我会用中国飞镖把那个家伙敲昏
Then I would knock the gun away with a Chinese throwing star.
菲比  快坐上脚踏车
Okay, Phoebe, just get on the bike...
我会扶着你帮你推  好吗
...and, hey, I'll hold you up and push you. Okay?
你不会放手
You won't let go?
-不  -你发誓
- No. - You swear?
我发誓
I swear.
-好吧  -来吧
- Okay. - Come on.
好了  要开始了  好吗
All right, here we go. All right?
-好  -好吗
- All right. - All right?
感觉不错吧   好了  试着踩踏板
Feel good? All right, try pedaling.
你做的很好 对  控制住车子
That's it, you're doing great. Yes, take control.
对对对
Yes, yes, yes!
不
Oh, no!
你发过誓的
You swore!
-我认为你骑得很好  -我真的很震惊
- I just thought you were doing so well. - I am shocked. Shocked!
大家都是那样学骑车的
It's a legitimate learning technique.
外面有人要糖吃
Hey, there's some people outside asking about candy.
他们必须得等  我只有一双手
They'll just have to wait, won't they? I only got two hands!
-需要帮助吗  -你不知道我的流程
- Need some help? - No, you don't know the system.
你会打乱我的流程
I don't need nobody messing with the system!
还有  婚礼前一周
By the way, the week before your wedding,
你可能会见不到我
you may not see a lot of me.
骗子  你好啊
Oh, hello, liar.
我很抱歉  我放了手
Look, I'm really sorry I let go of the bike.
我可能会没命的
I could've been killed, you know.
我知道
I know, I know.
但你能再试一次吗
But can we please try it again?
你只差一点就成功了  菲比
I mean, you were so close, Phoebe.
我很乐意
Well, I would love to...
但脚踏车被偷了  警察找不到嫌犯
...but the bike got stolen and the police have no suspects.
-菲比  -什么
- Phoebe. - What?
怎么会这样
What the hell?
你知道吗
All right, you know what?
如果你不学骑车  那我很抱歉
If you won't learn how to ride, then I'm sorry...
-我得把它收回去  -什么  为什么
...I have to take it back. - What? Why?
因为
Because it's...
就像你买了这把吉他
It'd be like you having this guitar...
却从来不弹它
...and never playing it.
这吉他希望被弹
Okay, this guitar wants to be played.
这辆脚踏车希望被骑
And this bike wants to be ridden.
如果你不骑它
And if you don't ride it...
你就是在扼杀它的灵魂
...you're killing its spirit.
脚踏车
The bike...
快死了
...is dying.
如果你这么在乎
All right. If you care enough
不惜满嘴胡言  那好吧
to make up that load of crap, okay.
很好
Great, great.
脚踏车会很开心的
You're making the bike very happy.
好吧  罗斯
Okay, Ross.
拜托请别死
Please don't die!
我们得在他们看到评估表前把它拿回来
To get the evaluation before they see it...
我们得溜进塞纳的办公室  他10点后才会来
...we gotta get into Zelner's office. He doesn't get in until 10.
但他的助理贝蒂一大早
But his assistant, Betty,
就会到办公室吃早餐
comes in early to eat breakfast at her desk.
-那还挺悲凉的  -贝蒂是挺悲凉的
- That's kind of sad. - Yeah, well, Betty's kind of sad.
所以我相信我可以用这些巧克力把她引开
Which is why I believe I can lure her away with these chocolates.
我引开她后  你就进去
While I distract her, you go in.
-我知道了  -行动吧
- Got it. - Let's roll.
瑞秋  你有空吗
Hello, Rachel. You got a minute?
当然塞纳先生  为您  什么都有
Yeah, sure, Mr. Zelner. For you? Anything. Minute.
很好
Okay, great.
计划中止
Abort the plan.
我要和你们俩同时谈话
Actually, I'd like to speak to both of you.
好
Okay.
你要点什么东西吗  巧克力
Well, can we get you anything, Mr. Zelner? Maybe some chocolates.
不谢谢  但可以给贝蒂
No, thanks, but I'll give these to Betty.
我看过你对泰格做的评估表
So I read your evaluation of Tag.
或许我该叫他的全名泰格"小可爱"琼斯
Or to use his full name, Tag "Sweet Cheeks" Jones?
你们之间有什么吗
Is something going on with you two?
你能想象如果我们俩约会吗
Oh, my God, can you imagine if there was?
会有什么后果啊
I mean, what would happen exactly?
我一定得上报
Well, I'd be forced to file a report.
得找法律部咨询
I'd have to consult with the legal department.
你们在公司的未来可能会受到影响
And your future at the company would be in jeopardy.
-就  -塞纳先生
- Well... - Mr. Zelner...
那份评估表是我写的
I filled in that evaluation.
-哦  不对  -是的
- Oh, no... - Yeah, yeah.
我以为这会很好玩
I thought it would be funny.
你写着你有可爱的小屁屁
You wrote that you have a cute tushy?
对  我的幽默感很奇怪
Yes. I have a weird sense of humor.
很奇怪地我以自己的屁股为荣
And I'm kind of strangely proud of my butt.
开这种玩笑太危险了  泰格
It's kind of a risky joke, Tag.
这到底是在画什么   我看不懂
What is this drawing? I can't figure it out.
它倒过来了  你得  那不重要
It's upside down, you gotta... It doesn't matter.
我不是没有幽默感
It's not like I don't have a sense of humor.
我甚至很喜欢写打油诗
Hell, I even enjoy a naughty limerick every now and then.
但时间跟地点是很重要的
There's a time and a place.
除非你现在有写打油诗的灵感
Unless you have a limerick right now.
没有吗  好吧  你知道我的传真机号码
No? Okay. Well, you've got my fax number.
我不敢相信你会那么做  那太贴心了
I can't believe you did that. That was sweet.
-别担心  -你可能会丢掉工作
- Don't worry about it. - You could've lost your job.
开什么玩笑  有着如此翘臀肯定能找到工作
Are you kidding me? With this cute butt, I'd find work.
谢谢  你太棒了
Thank you, you're great.
-你知道吗  -什么
- You know what? - What?
我很有成就感
I feel great.
事实上
In fact...
什么
What?
我花了好久才整理好
It's just... It took me so long to get that desk organized.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
看到啦
There it is.
这是闹哪样啊
What is going on?
我们在等糖果  把糖果拿出来
We're waiting for the candy. Bring out the candy!
小姐  把糖果拿出来
Yeah, lady, give us candy!
乔伊
Joey!
-怎么了  -你在干嘛
- What's up, buddy? - What are you doing?
等着那糖
Waiting to get candy.
进来
Get in here.
你不能在这抽烟
Hey, and you cannot smoke in here.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
糖果马上就到  巧克力还需15分钟放凉
The candy is coming! I need another 15 minutes for the chocolate to cool.
大家伙儿  保持安静
All right, everybody, just be quiet.
安静  安静  小声点儿
Be quiet! Be quiet! Pipe down!
你们都有什么毛病
What is the matter with you people?
这个女人想为大家
This woman was trying to
做点好事
do a nice thing for you.
她做糖果是为了认识你们
She was making candy so she could get to know all of you.
但我打赌你们没一个人知道她的名字
And I'll bet that not one of you can tell me her name.
我说对了吧
Am I right?
糖果小姐
Candy Lady?
才不是"糖果小姐"
No, not "Candy Lady."
如果我们知道了  我们能拿糖果吗
If we know it, can we have candy?
行了
All right, you know what?
随便吧  你们毁了这一切
Forget it, you've ruined it.
回家吧  你们毁了这一切
Go home. You've ruined it.
都是你们的错  你们毁了这一切
That's all wrong! You guys ruined everything. You ruined it!
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
你抽烟了
Did you smoke?
没啊  老烟枪女士直接喷了烟到我嘴里
No, smokes-a-lot lady blew smoke directly into my mouth.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我没事  但刚刚真的有点可怕
Fine, but it was really scary for a while.
有人会将恐吓纸条塞到门缝下
Someone slipped a threatening note under the door!
我很抱歉  我的暴力倾向发作了
Oh, yeah. Sorry about that. Mob mentality or whatever.
我简直不敢相信我办到了  我会骑车了
I can't believe it. I did it. I rode a bike!
从来没觉得我能学会  谢谢
I never thought I'd be able to do that. Thank you.
别谢我  谢你自己
Oh, hey, don't thank me. Thank yourself.
是你面对了自己的恐惧  终于克服了它们
You're the one who faced your fears and ultimately overcame them.
别唠唠叨叨的罗斯  这又不是课后辅导
Don't be so corny, Ross. It's not an After School Special.